http://www.lsuc.on.ca/privacy

COVID-19 Response     Corporate Statement, Updates & FAQs     Learn More
Show or hide this menu section
Coach and Advisor Network (CAN)
The Justicia Project
Contact Us (Equity)
Change your Status or Address
Join or Update Your Law Society Referral Service Subscription
Certified Specialists
How to Surrender Your Licence
Administrative Suspension and Reinstatement of Lawyers
Working or Associating with a Former or Suspended Licensee
Licensing Following Surrender or Revocation of Lawyer Licence
Tax Receipts
Practice Insurance (LAWPRO)
Q&A - Policies on the Annual Fee payment and Annual Report Filing
FAQs
Search CPD Articles (AccessCLE)
Accreditation Updates for CPD Providers
Coach and Advisor Network (CAN)
Change your Status or Address
Join or Update Your Law Society Referral Service Subscription
Obtain a Status Letter
Licensing Following Surrender or Revocation of Paralegal Licence
Tax Receipts
Q&A - Policies on the Annual Fee payment and Annual Report Filing
Paralegal Rules of Conduct
Coach and Advisor Network (CAN)
The Justicia Project
Contact Us (Equity)
FAQs
Search CPD Articles (AccessCLE)
Treasurer's Blog
Coach and Advisor Network (CAN)
Accreditation Criteria
Alternate Activities Application (PDF)
Application Form (PDF)
Sample Applications
CPD Accreditation for Providers (PDF)
Rule 9
Quick Reference Tool for Key Amendments to the Paralegal Rules of Conduct
Guidelines for Lawyers and Paralegals with Revoked Licenses
Permitted Criminal Code Summary Conviction Offences for Regulated Agents
Ontario Civil Legal Needs Project
Remembrance Day 2014: Honorary Call to commemorate First World War Centenary
Preparing to meet your lawyer or paralegal
Seeking legal help? Protect yourself.
FAQs about the Complaints Process
Complaints Information for First Nations, Métis and Inuit (FNMI) Peoples
Judicial and Tribunal Complaints Protocol
Complaints against LSO Benchers, Employees and Licensee Adjudicators
Show or hide this menu section
How do I become a lawyer in Ontario?
Articling Program Reporting Tool
Are you Acting as a Proxy for an Articling Principal?
Show or hide this menu section
How do I become a Paralegal in Ontario?
Withdrawals
Cataloguing Request Manual for County & District Law Libraries
Creating Persistent Links to AdvoCAT Catalogue Records or Searches
Privacy
This Privacy Statement is voluntarily provided by the Law Society of Ontario (“Society”) to inform users about features of the Society’s website (“Site”). This Privacy Statement does not apply in circumstances where the Law Society Act, regulations or by-laws may apply. Should you have questions or concerns about the Society’s obligations with respect to your use of this Site, you should consult the Law Society Act, regulations and by-laws.
Web analytics and Cookies
This Site uses Google Analytics. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect information about your visit to the Site, including your Internet Protocol address, information about the operating system of your computer or device, and information about your browser.
This information is processed by Google Analytics to generate statistics for the Society about patterns of user visits to the Site, including, among other things, the number of page visits, the number of unique page views, the average time spent on a page, traffic to the Site by hour of the day and day of the week, and geographic location of users. This information may be used to measure the use and performance of the Site and to improve the experience of visitors to the Site.  This information will not be used to identify individual users.
This Site also uses cookies set by the Society to map your session for the purpose of the survey and the intermediate page. A cookie is a small piece of data that a website sends to your browser for storage on your computer or device.  You may modify your browser to decline, delete or disable cookies. Please note that declining, deleting or disabling cookies may result in your inability to use certain parts of the Site as they are intended to be used.
Privacy Notice for LSO Store
This Privacy Statement does not apply to the LSO Store. To view the document applicable to the LSO Store, please consult the LSO Store Privacy Notice.
Changes
The Society may change any part of this Privacy Statement at any time. Changes will be effective when the changed Privacy Statement is posted on this Site. You should check the Privacy Statement frequently for changes by checking the date of “Last Updated” at the top of the document.
Terms or Concepts Explained
